<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Powers on Fourth World SRD</title>
    <link>https://oconnor0.github.io/fourth-world-srd/powers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Powers on Fourth World SRD</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://oconnor0.github.io/fourth-world-srd/powers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Arcane Spells</title>
      <link>https://oconnor0.github.io/fourth-world-srd/powers/arcane-spells/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oconnor0.github.io/fourth-world-srd/powers/arcane-spells/</guid>
      <description>Plasmic Dart. You send a magical dart streaking toward a creature that you can see.  Arcane, Attack, Spell, Ranged, Plasmic Level 0/1/2, Common Time: 1 Action Range: 100&#39; Target: 1/2/3 Creatures Attack: Automatic Hit Hit: 1d4 + 1 plasmic damage Miss:   Plasmic Touch. A touch from your hand, which glows with blue energy, blasts the target creature.  Arcane, Attack, Spell, Melee, Touch, Plasmic Level 0, Common Time: 1 Action Range: Melee Touch Target: 1 Creature Attack: ATTR vs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Divine Prayers</title>
      <link>https://oconnor0.github.io/fourth-world-srd/powers/divine-prayers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oconnor0.github.io/fourth-world-srd/powers/divine-prayers/</guid>
      <description>Focus on buffs, debuffs, defense, protection, healing, divination, truth, reality vs direct damage, illusion, etc. Support and social rather than combat; in general. Where do rituals show up?
Prayer List  Augury Bane Banish Beacon Bless. You bless the actions of one you touch, aiding their goals.  Divine, Utility, Spell, Touch Rank 1, Common, for Tier 1 Cast Time: 1 Action, 1 Minute? Duration: 1 Day, Sustained? Cost: 1 Bond Point Range: Touch Target: 1 Creature Effect: The creature gains a pool of 1 + your Tier d4 dice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Martial Exploits</title>
      <link>https://oconnor0.github.io/fourth-world-srd/powers/martial-exploits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oconnor0.github.io/fourth-world-srd/powers/martial-exploits/</guid>
      <description>How in the world do feats work here? What is there to upgrade?
How to differentiate block, dodge, and parry?
Crits/doubles/failure/miss/other triggers
  ? Double Strike. After a quick attack from your main-hand weapon, you make another with your off-hand weapon.
 Martial, Weapon, Deed, Melee, Attack Level 0/2, Common Time: 1 Action Range: Melee weapons (main-hand and off-hand) Target: 1 or 2 creatures Attack: ATTR - 2 vs. AC (one with your main-hand weapon, and another with your off-hand weapon) Hit: WPN/2WPN damage Miss:    Or just spend combo points to make attacks?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Primal Evocations</title>
      <link>https://oconnor0.github.io/fourth-world-srd/powers/primal-evocations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oconnor0.github.io/fourth-world-srd/powers/primal-evocations/</guid>
      <description>Acid Arrow. An arrow of acid springs from your hand and speeds to its target.  Primal, Evocation, Chemical, Implement, Attack Level 2/3/4/5, Common Time: 1 Action Range: 100&#39; Target: 1 creature Attack: ATTR vs. Reflex Hit: 4d4/5d4/6d4/7d4 chemical damage and ongoing 5/6/7/8 chemical damage (save ends) Miss: half damage   Fireball. A bright streak flashes from your pointing finger to a point you choose within range and then blossoms with a low roar into an explosion of flame.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technological Wonders</title>
      <link>https://oconnor0.github.io/fourth-world-srd/powers/technological-wonders/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://oconnor0.github.io/fourth-world-srd/powers/technological-wonders/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
